Just before we start, the question that was asked is, and then you might listen to this too.
Is there anything I can tell you that requires a certain majority of the research?
Okay.
We are going to call it one of the regular meeting of the Miami specials.
You'll feel the authority for today's date and time.
Item two is the invocation.
Follow the call, Crocodile Mine, from the Catholic Church here.
Thanks for being with us in that part.
And then you're going to the Father and of the Son and of the Holy Spirit.
God of creation.
We begin the season of springtime with whole plant dissipation.
Has daylight hours continued to lengthen.
Fill our civic leaders with energy, zeal, vitality, creativity.
In the United Vision for a plan of action that will enable all citizens
that will enhance all citizens of this community.
Provide all in the city of Miami with your graces, so that we willingly engage
and carrying out caring for your creation.
Each one of us is blessed by you with the responsibility of being a faithful steward.
Enable and motivate each soul to willingly put the unique gifts imparted by you
into service for the building up of your kingdom.
As we continue our letting journey to Easter joy, we ask this in Jesus's name,
in the name of the Father and of the Son and of the Holy Spirit.
Who's drumming the flag?
A part of the religion is the flag of the United States of America,
and to the Republic for which it stands.
One nation under high, in the list of the liberty of this is for.
I am the first public input and unscheduled personal pressures in the audience.
It was just to address the authority on the union of the agenda.
And being none, item five is custom agenda staff is recommending item six through eight
for the consent agenda.
Item ages to correction of a scrubbers error on a previous contract.
Any questions on any of those three items?
I entertain a motion to approve.
Most of them.
Second.
Roll ball place.
Something.
Four step.
Five.
Shelf.
All right.
I'm nine up there on the ETC five or sort of a pilot.
Yes sir.
Currently they haven't seen between 925 and 75 surveys back.
They're still going to the day to make sure there's not any new surveys.
Check in people's IP address.
They didn't come from the same.
They will give us a report at the end of next week.
We will bring kind of a preliminary.
Other results on April 4th.
And then April 18th will have a video conference.
I'm talking to David about doing the video conference with ETC Institute for them to actually show their presentation on the survey results in everything that they've
And kind of go through the report any questions for the council in the city we would have.
But try to probably take. Yes sir.
You said that how many back between 925 and 875?
So they sent out 39 at 3,923 surveys.
That's better than what they got us for the returns in the school.
I think that's what I appreciate what they're doing this are making sure they're no duplicates anything like that so we get a good result.
One thing I would like to also point out that we're working with Walton at this point and that is to bring fiber to all of our city facilities.
They've approached David Ballard.
I know David is up in the corner right now.
I T director but also Michael Richardson when he was still working with us.
I think some of that cost offsetting on where we already get our fiber would be a very good deal for the city number one.
Number two we would have gigabyte both up and down which would really improve our operational.
And then also if we do proceed then we're built what they would be doing in installing in our system.
They'd be able to basically branch off with that if they're going to be serving people in the community as well.
I do know that utilities especially electric utilities some of our kind of more distant areas like our airport or something.
We may have some of our line crews hang some of the fiber optic to be able to serve some of those areas as well.
That would all come from the budget line item that we already have for both.
So it wouldn't really be anything that would be a problem for the budget whatsoever.
So I think we're feeling very good about the ability to start offering gigabyte here and I think our operations will be phenomenally better if we do this and then we can start working from that.
You said hanging.
So those would go on.
Yes.
No, no, I think we just really be using our bucket trucks and using our current lines that we have right now.
Thanks Tyler.
Any questions for Tyler on that?
I know we've got a lot of information coming.
What's they want to point out that as as they finalize the report that those 925 days and 515 can change one way or a little bit because they you know that double checking all this surveys.
I'm 10 is new business and a new business day and anyone.
No, you're on it.
Staff reports are in your packet.
Any trustee community announcements on this meeting.
I'm 13 is a German.
We have a lot to adjourn.
Motion does that.